presonus.com 2015-06-07

# PreSonus | Privacy Policy

  * PRIVACY POLICY

### Your Consent to This Privacy Policy

By using our web site, you indicate that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted on our sites as well as the terms of our Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with this Policy or our Terms and Conditions, please do not use our site or provide any Personal Information to us.

### Sites Covered by This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all websites operated by or on behalf of PreSonus (www.PreSonus.com).

The PreSonus web site may provide links to third-party web sites that are beyond PreSonus’ control. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these third-party web sites, banners, sweepstakes and other advertisements or promotions that PreSonus may sponsor or participate in on web sites owned by third parties. These third-party web sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. PreSonus encourages you to review the privacy policy of any company (which may differ from PreSonus’) before submitting your Personal Information. PreSonus does not endorse and makes no guarantee or representation as to the sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of the content or privacy policy of any third-party web site to which you may be linked from a PreSonus site. Since PreSonus does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. PreSonus encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

PreSonus will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number or email address (“Personal Information”) through its web site unless you provide it to us yourself. Circumstances in which you may choose to provide us Personal Information include: providing your name and mailing address while entering a contest so that we may notify you if you win, providing your email address so that we may send you information you request, signing up to receive our newsletter, or registering as a user so that you may gain access to a particular section of a site. If you do not wish for us to collect any Personal Information about you, do not submit it to us.

When PreSonus collects Personal Information that you provide to us, PreSonus may store, process and use it for the following purposes: to send you information you have requested such as information about us, promotional information about our products, or details of any offers or promotions; to assist us in improving our products, services or the content of our site; to contact you in connection with a contest or promotion, or for our own internal marketing and research purposes.

The web site you entered may also collect Personal Information from you about a third party (e.g., the site might allow you to send an email or message to a friend, in which case we will need that person's name and email address). Please note that we use such information only for the specified purpose (e.g., to deliver the email message) and we will not contact the third party again by email unless and until the third party contacts us. We may also enhance your Personal Information by linking it to data obtained from third parties, such as non-personally identifiable information (e.g., demographic and geographic characteristics) as well as other publicly available data such as census information. Such enhanced information allows us to provide our users with a more customized experience.

### With Whom We May Share Information

In the course of doing business, PreSonus may employ other companies to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, at times PreSonus may retain third parties to analyze, update and correct data we collect on our web sites, including Personal Information, to help us improve our products, our database and our web site. In addition, we may share Personal Information with agents, suppliers, fulfillment houses and other third parties to allow delivery of prizes, information, products or services. These suppliers and other third parties may have access to your Personal Information if it is needed to perform their functions for PreSonus, but they are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information in any way other than the intended use.

PreSonus will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and will only disclose your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy and/or with your explicit consent. Third parties are not permitted to sell the information we provide to them, to market directly to you, or to disclose it in any other way without your explicit consent. PreSonus will provide you with notice if our privacy policy changes and an opportunity to reject such changes. We let you change your personal information so that you can keep it up to date. PreSonus uses safe, secure technology and other privacy protection programs to keep your personal information secure on PreSonus.com.

You agree that PreSonus may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

You agree that PreSonus may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, PreSonus encourages you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on the notification preferences page. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time.

PreSonus cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, PreSonus can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address and User ID history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy, PreSonus will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, PreSonus can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company name to proper authorities under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, PreSonus cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although PreSonus uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, PreSonus does not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain private.

### Important Note Regarding Cross-Border Data Transfers

The laws and regulations in different countries impose different requirements on the Internet and data protection. PreSonus is located in the United States, as are the servers that make our site available worldwide. All matters relating to our sites are governed by the laws of Louisiana in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please note that any information you provide will be transferred to the United States, which may not have privacy laws similar to those in your own country, and that by submitting the information you authorize this transfer.

### Use of Cookies

Like most companies, while you are visiting one of our sites, we may store some information (called a "cookie") on your computer’s hard drive. This allows us to tailor our site to your individual preferences and save time if you visit the site again. It also helps us study the browsing patterns of our visitors and improve our web site design and content. Most internet browsers allow you to set them to warn you before a cookie is stored or block cookies altogether.

Through the use of "cookies," PreSonus may automatically collect some technical information which is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this include the type of internet browser you are using and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to one of our sites. We may aggregate this type of information for market research purposes and to improve our web site. We do not use "cookies" to obtain personal information about any of our visitors.

### Forums

From time to time, portions of our site may allow you to post information which other visitors to the site will be able to access (such as on a “forum”). In the event that you choose to post information in this context, it becomes generally available to the public, and we have no ability to control or limit its use by visitors to our sites. Therefore, PreSonus encourages you not to post any information you consider private or sensitive on our sites.

### Important Note to Children

Before providing your name, address, email address or any other Personal Information to anyone on the Internet, be sure to ask your parents’ permission.

### Data Protection and Security

PreSonus takes commercially reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure. All access to the information we collect is subject to physical, electronic and managerial restrictions to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse. Notwithstanding the foregoing, PreSonus cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk.

### Manage Your Personal Information; Unsubscribe

PreSonus offers you the ability to automatically review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the Site and entering in the new information yourself. Generally, we will not modify your personal information based on your request because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. You can change your User Id, email address, contact information and user preferences by accessing the preferences and setup section of the Site. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once posted, you may not be able to change or remove any public postings made on the Site including our chat rooms or other message areas.

Upon your request, we will deactivate your account and all associated information from our active databases. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

PreSonus will retain in our files some personal information you have requested to remove to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our User Agreement and comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will be deactivated from public and member viewing and will only be available to select PreSonus personnel.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

In the event we change our privacy policy, we will post these changes promptly on this page. We encourage you to check this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current privacy policy.

### Privacy and New Technologies

PreSonus may obtain personal information about you from a variety of outside sources including third party mailers and new technology sources. PreSonus obtains that information in order to design consumer offers. If you do not wish to receive any of these offers or products, you may notify us and we will make every effort to insure you are not contacted.

### How to Contact Us

In the event you wish to contact us in connection with this Privacy Policy, you may mail us at:

**PreSonus Audio Electronics**  
18011 Grand Bay Court   
Baton Rouge, LA 70809 USA
